[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "What's wrong with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "Well, the problem is several things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 57, "question": "And what is wrong with giving the poorer sections, the needier sections of society a bit of hope and even if for most of them it turns out in the end to be a hope that isn't realized?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "IN", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 58, "answer": "Well, because it's false hope.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "You've got no way of knowing, have you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "Well, we actually do know it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "And I guarantee, most everybody realizes I probably won't win tonight, but what if?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJS", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", ",", "CC", "WP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "I mean, you make it sound wonderfully harmless.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Massachusetts", "California"]}, "docId": "121128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "Now that is a huge chunk of change, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "It's -- government gambling has been a failed revenue source across the country, whether it's Massachusetts, California, you name it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$4.7 billion"]}, "docId": "121128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ":", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "$", "CD", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "What is actually your problem with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "But if you have sales -- that money comes from $4.7 billion worth of sales.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "TO", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 185, "question": "Which one should I do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "CD", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 186, "answer": "Well, I'm going to sidebar for just a second on you and then come back to that if I can.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "EX", "VBZ", "CD", "CD", "WDT", "-NONE-", "VB", "VBG", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ":", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 207, "question": "I mean, there's got to be somebody tomorrow possibly who'll be re-watching this avidly as I'm sure they do every night, and saying, Dave Ramsey, I just won half a billion dollars, you know, what are you talking about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NN", "RB", "WP", "-NONE-", "VB", "JJ", "DT", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBG", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 208, "answer": "And there's 175 million that'll be watching -- I hope your ratings were that good tomorrow night -- that didn't win.", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["a billion dollars"], "PERSON": ["Dave Ramsey"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "Does America suffer when taxes are slightly higher in terms of its economic prosperity, or is that just a bit of a myth?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "NN", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "JJR", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "Well, I think there's a lot of theories out there running around and you know I've got the formal education in finance degree and so I've studied economics like a lot of folks have, and I was formally schooled in Keynesian economics.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "Steven Rattner, is there a principle or is it just bloody minded news now by Republicans led by Grover Norquist, we shall not pay anymore taxes ever?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "VBN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNPS", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "At some point, of course, there is such a thing as too much tax.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steven Rattner", "Grover Norquist"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBG", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 330, "question": "Putting your pragmatic hats on, if you were in that negotiating room, Emil Henry, what would the deal be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "DT", "NN", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "Broadly speaking, here's where I think this has to end up.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Emil Henry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "Steven Rattner, if you were in that room and that was on the table what would you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "I would say you need to have a compromise that's more in the middle.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steven Rattner"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "Is this becoming a tax on the poor?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "It is a tax on the poorer and the numbers bare that out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "I mean, it's a gimmick, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "It is a gimmick.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "Were you surprised?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "MILEY: Not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 499, "question": "What should they be thinking now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 500, "answer": "Well, first of all, my preference, my preference is for the president to be more progressive.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "And very quickly, what's the number one priority to try and eradicate poverty, would you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "RB", ",", "WDT", "POS", "DT", "NN", "CD", "NN", "TO", "NN", "CC", "VB", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "Jobs, jobs, jobs, and jobs with a living wage.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["this almost 23 years"]}, "docId": "121128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "CD", "NNS", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 565, "question": "Do you appreciate that, too?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 566, "answer": "Well, I've got to tell you honestly, Piers, I've been doing this almost 23 years, and there has been nothing but goodness coming as far as I can see.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York Lottery"]}, "docId": "121128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "And Yolanda, are you allowed to play the lottery or not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "Nobody in the New York Lottery can play.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Yolanda"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$250"], "LOCATION": ["Georgia"]}, "docId": "121128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "$", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 584, "question": "What is the biggest amount of money you've won on a scratch card?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 585, "answer": "Oh, I think I won $250 in the state of Georgia.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 587, "question": "You decided not to retire?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 588, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 592, "question": "If you won -- obviously, I know you can't, I'm talking metaphorically, if you won a half a billion dollars, as the Powerball now is tonight what would you spend it on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "RB", "VBZ", "VBN", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 593, "answer": "I think right now -- I mean I've always thought I'd buy an exotic island or a bunch of cars for friends and family.", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["a billion dollars"]}}]